http://www.moscownaz.org/privacy-statement

Contact Us
Moscow Church of the Nazarene Privacy PolicyMoscow Church of the Nazarene is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Moscow Church of the Nazarene Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Moscow Church of the Nazarene website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONMoscow Church of the Nazarene collects personally identifiable information, such as, but not limited to, your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Moscow Church of the Nazarene also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as, but not limited to, your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Moscow Church of the Nazarene. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Moscow Church of the Nazarene for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Moscow Church of the Nazarene Web site.Moscow Church of the Nazarene encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Moscow Church of the Nazarene so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Moscow Church of the Nazarene is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Moscow Church of the Nazarene and Moscow Church of the Nazarene family of Web sites.USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONMoscow Church of the Nazarene collects and uses your personal information to operate the Moscow Church of the Nazarene Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Moscow Church of the Nazarene also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Moscow Church of the Nazarene and its affiliates. Moscow Church of the Nazarene may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Moscow Church of the Nazarene does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Moscow Church of the Nazarene may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Moscow Church of the Nazarene may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Moscow Church of the Nazarene, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Moscow Church of the Nazarene does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Moscow Church of the Nazarene may keep track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Moscow Church of the Nazarene, in order to determine what Moscow Church of the Nazarene services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content within Moscow Church of the Nazarene to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Moscow Church of the Nazarene Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Moscow Church of the Nazarene or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Moscow Church of the Nazarene; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Moscow Church of the Nazarene, or the public.USE OF COOKIESThe Moscow Church of the Nazarene Web site may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Moscow Church of the Nazarene's pages, or register with Moscow Church of the Nazarene site or services, a cookie helps Moscow Church of the Nazarene to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Moscow Church of the Nazarene Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Moscow Church of the Nazarene features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Moscow Church of the Nazarene services or Web sites you visit.SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONMoscow Church of the Nazarene secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Moscow Church of the Nazarene secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENTMoscow Church of the Nazarene will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Moscow Church of the Nazarene encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Moscow Church of the Nazarene is protecting your information.CONTACT INFORMATIONMoscow Church of the Nazarene welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Moscow Church of the Nazarene has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Moscow Church of the Nazarene. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Come Visit Us!
Visit
